wonderful meeting
[music]
last time where he
said that we need to help people and what the
other guy said he said I can't
even help the environment how can I help
but he convinced us that we can
help others
forest ability we have the channel of
Sweden which ultimately is in the center of your body
and then he began an interesting section
which says not only you have a
good correct body but you also have
teachings
you have yet to possess and within these
teachings you have bad but also within the
waving you have you clearly the diamond
path
then he said that all schools
agree for example they all agree
without division within the schools that you can
achieve enlightenment and
[music]
then he mentions jetsian
which says that you can
achieve this in 12 years this is tantra
and I am talking with
this question
and
that in three years and three months
[music]
three months so sorry for the delay
before many holy beings of the past
will achieve this and I think that if you somehow
you say well I have not seen anyone who
achieved but
[music]
then I would say my they  I haven't seen
anyone who has achieved this, so of course you have
n't seen anyone who has achieved this, but for
this you need to be close to
achieving it yourself, and I've never
even read about it,
but it's the same
thing, that it also has seeds to
protest about this,
you need seeds to achieve
this, not if you've heard that you can
achieve it in 3 years and 3 months, you can do
this very well
[music]
merging anniversary anniversary anniversary of the
tragedy anniversary you can do
weeks sea view
they say that this is the
last five out of five hundred, what does this
mean, this is from bad days, someone once said
super diamond facet Chagalov risk and
decay times
says that when
you drink tea and leaves and soot tea leaves
settle at the bottom of the glass, this is such
garbage at the bottom of the glass, we time
[music] right
now we live in such times of
garbage at the bottom of the glass,
we have never seen more times in
all the lives that you had
before, you have never seen better,
you have a body that works
well enough, so you, you have
time and you have space and you have
Diamond Mountain,
thank you
reverend, what happened to
other people who are preparing spaghetti.
There are two famous meditations that
mention
sweeping the lion roaring sugar.
This is the 2nd type of Lensky meditator, and which is
very famous to
many. It is
said that they achieved enlightenment
during their lifetime. They went to places that are very
similar to Diamond Mountain. They
found the 3rd center, only there were no
colder stores there and they did not achieve this and the
crown for 50 dollars. What does this mean? A
guy who stays in
the desert in the mountains. This is what it means. And his
name is
something like Mr. Diamond Edge.
It's something like Gars and among them,
Mr. Mountain. Connecting
their bodies was not something different from
our body. We
have less fluff in the store. If
they did this there, we can
[music]
Come on, an hour, a strange story.
Circle. This is a small town in
Tibet called that. There
was a guy there who had a
problem with his leg. They got wet without sticks.
He
rode a
donkey and
soon he...
This guy who had a
problem with his leg... He sat
on a donkey and he
himself ran away and
in general
something
happened he ran away and the
coolest ride in life there is
such and such an idiom
we can ride a coat and before
people had a long coat when they
rode and
we need to think about this that Milarepa is
like one on which we can just
accidentally
[music]
ride on him take his example the
example of these people who will achieve the
goal and in the same way achieve the goal
but annayake
please repeat their slave of the lamp and the
lamp
and water
is accomplished
[music]
we do not avoid meditation on lanas why you
diseases
[music]
this is a disease that killed half of the people in
Europe
meditate you
can be
like for example reading very lessons
teachings such
[music]
only or there fight tandra but if
someone says but he can in a moment to you for
an hour and constancy we say but
maybe we kind of want cooler
Masha tendency to be attracted by
deeper and
themes instead of and
titating on lambre
you don't know.
.  murder means you don't know what's
important
[music]
you need to do meditation Lavrin everyone
can take one of these pictures there
were more than a thousand pictures
the most competition and you can take any of them that's
why they are here you ca
n't say that you don't have
any and
that's how we feel about
meditation meditation for time
and this guy we have this
we when someone tells us let's
meditate
show the last ones it seems to me on Russia
yes this is the guy with a bad leg
who accidentally
fell on a donkey don't forget you will have a
test on all these pictures the
base or foundation is the key to the
code word for the body or when you
speak in the camp places and
say you need to know that you have a
foundation
you have the
right body and mind with all its channels
like the Venetian canal and a
mind that can understand emptiness and
totem you have a foundation tea
means not having yet
not sure that you will have another million
years or something like that chance when
you will have access and Darvish and access for
free this is a very strange thing
we live in countries where we
have free access to  drama but there are
many other countries in which you can't
have no right why is it available for free
in wine you can't you are
lucky that you have such an
opportunity and
this doesn't mean you don't know when how much
time
you you video to get to this
he and
even the body that was created by
millions of such efforts it is very
doubtful that it is difficult to
get it again
even a completely
healthy body and
intellectual
but then to meet such teachings
that you meet assessment by this
will be very very in order to
find this in humanity
when I was young I met such a
proposal when they bragged
about
sun cafe
but when you understand a lot of
background knowledge
especially when we study both darmu
classics when you understand and
try to practice you
really understand that the female
understood and
I don't brag about it later I will not introduce
beta
1 now slightly the same as the other
glow is not so important and
who achieved this who
[music]
was able to
understand I am not loyal to 1
but if you read the film you will understand
study and you will understand in Russian this guy is
definitely all sorts and you really
understand and
give u  You begin your own
life-changing experience and
often you have incredible experiences
or in
your life which you begin to
receive new words, maybe a
guy gives out a strange world, he became a
bow, he
lived in a small village which
eye was famous for its crafty fields, he is from a
small,
he is from a village and a sound village is a
big difference between me,
let's put on a show, I did not call the mountains, we can do
without him, what could be here, this is a
level of
layers, this is something for us to think about, there is
some secret in this,
not in meeting these teachings, this is
very rare and we are working on books in a
mix on funny nuts
all these books and not transferring a bag by and
you, of course, are all a little
spoiled, you have not seen
there are 300 thousand others for squid and ourselves
new
plums from wine
because
we translate the best books,
you work on cream happy and this is the
whole point of mixed nuts
here is a picture for you it will
turn out maybe a little strange, but
you are unlikely to meet
Sagittarius this guy again, a stupid guy
who sold the house
as we bought, for example,
cream for our sleep company Med it
was very, very difficult I
asked a
business partner why it is so hard
to buy a skyscraper  he said think
we only buy one or two in your
life
usually when you buy something for
input they have to be
nice to you so that
they yes you come back to him again
buy something else for
you will return to
[music]
this body of
teachings in this
political course how much is
there plus seven years more than 10 thousand
pages of distillations I told them there will be a
day when we will not be together all
grew and dark
different sides these classes will end one day
only
out of
80 there are 3,476 left somewhere went in
another different directions don't think that this will
remain on yourself this landrin
sad sentence that people in
this audience will die one by one and
then the last
they will all leave it came one day there is no
one else and there became more than thousands of
people if you think about it they
all disappeared them become with their religion
practical that this is a
very sad thing this is happening
you are still not divorced
funny
about this that while we are still not
divorced not happening you
need to think about what you would like to
get under the features the door appears and
because to be rubles so that at
least in these  I went to classes, it won't
leave the company, I would like to
get the bodhichitta apple so that I
get a good chance, a good start
because you can't become a Buddha, so you
need to leave and the
goal is not to walk through the planets,
once it obliges
all universes, personally, I like
what happens later,
I like the picture,
looks at my next one, I do it
because he lost the current ones,
I'll tell you there is something moisture if
you,
if you were lucky enough to sit on in
time before you got so old,
you can't help but get sick, and I
started when I was
29 years ago,
I
know, I understand, I
understand
[music]
this is a blessing to sit when
you don't believe it,
it's to preserve your, then when you get old,
old, oh my god, it was true, I'm so glad
that it's in my head
[music]
it's impossible to talk about
life because you
[music]
will be glad that you heard about it
but don't practice it
[music]
then when the time comes, you will get
older, you will get old, and when you
get to
your meditation house,
try the Louvre
I think most
of our audience are so
respectable I was like
just try to put this in your
head
beliefs until you believe in
[music]
impermanence so that you don't see
that people are dying around you and
just put this
squirrels collect nuts
they crunch
I sat with my teacher for over 25 years
in the Lavra my and I listened I respected him I
understood intellectually that this makes
sense
but I didn't realize it until I became
much older a
new word to get to you
[music]
whip there is such a word in
American English
young guy just
just put this information in yourself
on the pot and disk in the Louvre of your mind and
then you can use
by the way if you achieve about the difference the
cool thing is
that you not only get not
only what you hope for but it is
also an opportunity for everyone else
what they want
if you don't want something yourself at
least do it this is the
best thing that can be done for you and
for other people I ca
n't sit here and repeat this over
and over again
but in fact if you do it once you will
jump  between planets talk or
other living beings talk with
other living beings
about you don't talk about this
experience won't believe we call it what
[music]
you kind of take communion these people
say goodbye to this and
it was has
become more nonsense today
but
if you get very old it was
better of course to talk about it
if you do this if you have a
meeting with billions of people in half an hour and
convince them that you will take care
they
of course this is
fulfilling all your own dreams
if they have for themselves then
get the barhi account for the sake of other people and
here he begins very-very these are
such small we will die out stories
that you do not find
philosophical here are very small
interesting stories in the tradition of skin on
Christian history growth we
Christian history on the
new
in the New Testament and
hundreds of thousands of people
spent time
[music]
studied and
here in this story
[music] a
carpenter example such a time tells
stories and then people 2 thousand years of
history of
life
she finds much-much in
defense of these stories Milan Rome stories
exactly like that they are similar to such stupid
stories but in them you can but  you can
meditate all your life you can
meditate not all your life you
will go for they are simple
they look like that
such simple stories
grove and I have to do
slow down your voice
[ __ ]
I translators apparently
[music]
people
find a lot of meaning in them and so there was a
famine in a certain country
there was not a certain family
suffering from hunger
and
with them they were very
sick from hunger and
die
this is what can happen next in
Ukraine club
first you blow up a
store and then everyone will start to
starve and
one day they found a
piece of meat
many Tibetans are not vegetarians and they
say
since they could not grow green
plants at
high altitude in the mountains that they
were not vegetarians many my monastery
was Roman which is a very very big
change after 2000 in any case
they found some
small
piece of dried meat and my father thought
to himself I
could cut it up and
divide it between all the family members we would
all have the opportunity to get the
same number of
bites but each family member will
get just one or two bites
and
this will not stop the
famine
this is not  will stop
starvation
we will all die anyway we will all die
in three days instead of today
if I give
this to everyone
half it will just stop it for a couple of
days
but if
in contrast
I ate the whole piece myself
if n 7 the whole piece of meat myself
then I will have enough strength to
find more food myself
then I can come back before they
die this is very interesting and a moral
dilemma
I can dodge and help them and
he very
carefully to say with this
motivation to help others he ate the
whole piece
he found he went
and and and saved the family and you need to think about
it there is
time to take
care of yourself
in order to help others
[music]
there is time diamond burning your us
to spend kind and
vennym and
we are very used to processing in
order to help other people we do not
apply translated I can
think but maybe it would be better to
restore
fight on the commission and
find time to eat meat
myself and
[music]
find internal resources get
together find the module dropped
instead you are trying to
help everyone
scatter in order to help
it is not easy it is very difficult
therefore understand what you need to do
ignore Ukraine by  tigrik what is the
right time to have an
impact like in this story
[music]
so it is very important because I am again a
teacher
who was what was
[music]
passed
brunette
[music]
there are many solutions that I did not need to
make in life because 25 years
with my teacher the
armpits of our country New Jersey
is where they make
gasoline and the
northern part only Jersey is very strong well
what are the gasoline factories and
I passed them every day on the way in the
questionnaires it is called fatal
fatal
cancer alley and
if you ask me where the only
place in them I would not want to live is
New Jersey
when I was growing up we threw stones
people threw stones at cars that
had a
license plate and then I learned
that it is better to teach
I had to go there sometimes
we have to go where
you would not want to go with this brings
you closer to your teacher and then you can
ask him
what if I want to go and cry 3 but on the
other hand and signed up to help
refugees from Ukraine what is better to do and
therefore it is good to have a teacher and
I had him many, many  years and I
still have a teacher's board and this is a big
decision that you need to think about
maybe you will have to go to New Jersey
I had so many friends
from other regions who asked about the
versions made
we later they called me and said help
me when I'm
older this is the description
here is the picture that conveys this
feeling like
[music]
give you the feeling that
this journey gives you this path if you need
I would suggest you keep this
picture next to glory it is very similar and
you can
[music]
it's good
to look at it
show
it is very similar you
can make a copy of this photo
put it on the bellows
as a screensaver
what is on my phone
okay 100 dollars if you can recognize
this picture except the stands and
[music]
the library
it is very very similar to the diamond lesson
and
they built before the
dynasties
it was used in the
late Han dynasty and
they found one of the walls in which the price
was
part of a cave and they broke this wall and did
not find diamonds there
courts of the diamond screen which was
the oldest book that was
printed in the world and it was not
built then  This library
module is exactly this picture on the
phone
look at a couple of times a day and the picture and
he says here that especially when you
practice tantra look at this
picture a couple of times a day
he says
I would
[music]
tobacco sew so that you never do
even oh mani padme hum
one circle so that at this moment you
look at this picture and
if you are in a monastery and you do
this a
little blackmail that
you should not have a kitchen in
your own room
we must do a situation in the morning
in order to go in general
if you can't do it then you
can take it to the
bartender
just sometimes return to this
motivation that you have what you want to
get
if you continue to look
we strengthen and
understanding that the
planets and the planets of this wall themselves
are already pictures in your day this is the
only way you can
visit them half an hour in any let it be
true and therefore it is logical
every time when you have a few
minutes I take and picture in
my special room for meditation first
I check dreams nabu planets and
because the planets are also pictures your world
is pictures
bend to these pictures even if you are
just waiting  breakfast at this time, then this
will become your reality,
team, I will continue the next lesson, we
have four more, many
discussions in different types, in all chats
there is
approximately, in general, what is this, in
general, 4 sugar canes and here is a
beautiful good picture of Arbat,
next is the next lesson, this is the
wrong picture, it
should be a picture of a sugar clearing in
any case, have you ever been to
India?
It's cool, they grow a
lot of sugar,
and there are thousands of
trucks filled with sugar
cane,
children run around and several canes always disappear from them,
sugar, conduct how children run after a
truck of
cane and
then they
gnaw off the
outer part,
eat the inner part, and there is such a very
strong
sugar
chess,
if you have more money, then you can
just
go to the guy who
[music]
breaks
sugar cane with a
special machine and
instead of Coca-Cola, a
drink made from sugar cane with
water from
[music]
with water from
which you can get a tree, the
inner part is tasty and
later the peel is very tasty, a little
sugar  The owner, the
outer part is just creepy, it's
not the same as
usual, it's just a peel.
At first, when you learn mahi chita,
someone turns you off to distinguish and you
look at the planets on your phone during
your special meditation at home.
The name of this is something like sugar
cane and extraction, but it's not
real. It's just the
first step. Is
it connected? Then do
we call it bodhicitta? Is it really possible?
And chita, no, it's not the
same as the inside. No, it's
sweet. Just imagine that you
can visit all the planets in the universe.
Has a personal interview with everyone, with
every living person. Is
it pleasant? Is it tasty? Yes, you
can kind of chew the
outer part like this and try the
taste.
There is also some definite connection between the
order
and sugar cane. Sometimes it's
called a clan. Collected waters. A certain
flank had something to do with this.
Maybe there is some kind of connection.
So,
guys, let's do it. Derek. Chew these
a little
[music]
sugar cane. Thank you, Sasha.